

SENIOR FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Details

Mumbai, Maharashtra +91 8097326944 gawthamnadar18@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Education

B.Sc. – IT, Wilson College, Mumbai. (2017)

Skills

ReactJS

NodeJS

Angular

JavaScript

Core Java

MySQL

HTML & CSS

Git

JIRA

Core Competencies

Teamwork, Problem Solving and Decision Making, Strong Learning Agility

Languages

English, Hindi, Tamil, Marathi.

Hobbies

Playing Cricket and Kabaddi.

Profile

Highly motivated and diligent software developer with 4+ years of expertise in a variety of development areas like back-end services, front-end services, database models. Expert in working in an agile work environment, using project tracking tools like Jira, and version controlling with Git. Scaling new heights of success and leaving a mark of excellence.

Employment History

Senior Technology Consultant at Ernst and Young LLP, Mumbai

MARCH 2022 — PRESENT

Client: HSBC (Wholesale IT - Banking Sector)

Project: **SmartServe** - Global digital platform used for client outreach for wholesale clients across Global Banking.

Responsibilities:

- Improved and expanded project platforms using ReactJS and Redux to develop rich user interface to provide more functionalities and enhanced user experience, did peer code reviews and improved overall test coverage. Ensure that UI works flawlessly on all browsers and devices supported, maintaining accessibility and browser compatibility.
- 2. Writing reusable code and maintained documentation to a standard which makes it quick and easy to maintain the code in the future.
- 3. Collaborating with team to identify and fix technical problems and analyzing users' needs and then finding features to serve them.
- 4. Expertise usage of GitLab & JIRA for version control and tracking units.

Software Developer at AQM Technologies PVT LTD, Mumbai

MAY 2019 — FEBRUARY 2022

Projects handled:

- 1. DMS (Document Management System)
- 2. **HRMS** (Human Resource Management System)
- 3. Online CV Maker

Responsibilities:

Developed a CRUD Web Application based on MVC using technologies such as ReactJS, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MySQL Server, HTML, CSS.

Internships

Junior Software Developer at ETI Infosystem, Mumbai

MARCH 2019 — MAY 2019

Junior Android Developer at I-Tech Media, Mumbai

JULY 2018 — OCTOBER 2018

Courses

Post Graduate Program in Software Engineering. (Java Specialization), NIIT

CCNA (Routing & Switching), RST Forum

DECEMBER 2016